{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823499638","data":{"timestamp":" 946823499638"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" faa21022-a68a-4006-9cef-8026bad5d684"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823499699","data":{"timestamp":" 946823499699"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 8835cfdb-2c0f-4537-9887-64ac9a98848c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_28"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda utanipa chungwa mbivu wakati huo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823510930","data":{"timestamp":" 946823510929"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NDEVU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEVU"," userResponse":" NDEVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823516272","data":{"timestamp":" 946823516272"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NDEVU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823517844","data":{"timestamp":" 946823517843"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NJIWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIWA"," userResponse":" NJIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823520460","data":{"timestamp":" 946823520460"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NJIWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIWA"," userResponse":" NJIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823522050","data":{"timestamp":" 946823522049"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NGUMI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUMI"," userResponse":" NGUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823525604","data":{"timestamp":" 946823525603"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NGUMI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUMI"," userResponse":" NGUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823527227","data":{"timestamp":" 946823527226"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NGURUWE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823531564","data":{"timestamp":" 946823531564"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NGURUWE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823533169","data":{"timestamp":" 946823533168"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823539352","data":{"timestamp":" 946823539352"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" START_NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823541868","data":{"timestamp":" 946823541867"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823543471","data":{"timestamp":" 946823543470"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZI"," userResponse":" NAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823547763","data":{"timestamp":" 946823547763"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823549316","data":{"timestamp":" 946823549316"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYWELE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823552879","data":{"timestamp":" 946823552879"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYWELE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823554450","data":{"timestamp":" 946823554450"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYATI"," userResponse":" NYATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823558259","data":{"timestamp":" 946823558259"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823559807","data":{"timestamp":" 946823559807"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823564763","data":{"timestamp":" 946823564763"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823566343","data":{"timestamp":" 946823566343"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NGOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOMA"," userResponse":" NGOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823568810","data":{"timestamp":" 946823568810"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NGOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOMA"," userResponse":" NGOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823570364","data":{"timestamp":" 946823570364"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NDIZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823574340","data":{"timestamp":" 946823574340"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NDIZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823575894","data":{"timestamp":" 946823575894"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823579446","data":{"timestamp":" 946823579445"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823581019","data":{"timestamp":" 946823581019"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYAYO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823584820","data":{"timestamp":" 946823584820"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYAYO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823586388","data":{"timestamp":" 946823586388"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NGUO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823589455","data":{"timestamp":" 946823589454"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NGUO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823591076","data":{"timestamp":" 946823591076"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NG'OMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823591093","data":{"timestamp":" 946823591093"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NG'OMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823595454","data":{"timestamp":" 946823595453"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NG'OMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823597379","data":{"timestamp":" 946823597379"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NG'OMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823598927","data":{"timestamp":" 946823598927"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823602249","data":{"timestamp":" 946823602249"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823603801","data":{"timestamp":" 946823603801"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NDEGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823606820","data":{"timestamp":" 946823606820"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NDEGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823608380","data":{"timestamp":" 946823608380"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZI"," userResponse":" NZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823611256","data":{"timestamp":" 946823611256"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823612809","data":{"timestamp":" 946823612809"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYUMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823616330","data":{"timestamp":" 946823616330"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NYUMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823617879","data":{"timestamp":" 946823617879"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NANASI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANASI"," userResponse":" NANASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823622288","data":{"timestamp":" 946823622288"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NANASI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823624296","data":{"timestamp":" 946823624295"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" NANASI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823624460","data":{"timestamp":" 946823624460"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" NANASI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823632760","data":{"timestamp":" 946823632759"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 1602b923-6b38-413c-9ac3-19ed5ead1cea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" NANASI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823671190","data":{"timestamp":" 946823671190"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823684447","data":{"timestamp":" 946823684447"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823696797","data":{"timestamp":" 946823696797"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823710851","data":{"timestamp":" 946823710851"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823719334","data":{"timestamp":" 946823719334"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823734557","data":{"timestamp":" 946823734557"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823747339","data":{"timestamp":" 946823747339"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823759670","data":{"timestamp":" 946823759670"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823790797","data":{"timestamp":" 946823790797"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823801871","data":{"timestamp":" 946823801870"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823812608","data":{"timestamp":" 946823812608"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823825752","data":{"timestamp":" 946823825752"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823827842","data":{"timestamp":" 946823827842"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823837440","data":{"timestamp":" 946823837440"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823845083","data":{"timestamp":" 946823845083"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823848560","data":{"timestamp":" 946823848560"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823854328","data":{"timestamp":" 946823854328"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823854951","data":{"timestamp":" 946823854951"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823865881","data":{"timestamp":" 946823865881"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823876563","data":{"timestamp":" 946823876562"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946823884030","data":{"timestamp":" 946823884030"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824039303","data":{"timestamp":" 946824039302"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 09979443-e795-46c4-b66e-0b7bccd36b33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824039412","data":{"timestamp":" 946824039412"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 14e9d92e-a6be-47b0-8597-a5c83a80340e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824068459","data":{"timestamp":" 946824068459"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" d9d6a230-521d-4fad-9749-cf352ad0ba1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_L-N-F"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824071924","data":{"timestamp":" 946824071924"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" d9d6a230-521d-4fad-9749-cf352ad0ba1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_J-N-I"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824075361","data":{"timestamp":" 946824075360"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" d9d6a230-521d-4fad-9749-cf352ad0ba1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-Z"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824078730","data":{"timestamp":" 946824078730"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" d9d6a230-521d-4fad-9749-cf352ad0ba1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-E-G"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824082288","data":{"timestamp":" 946824082288"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" d9d6a230-521d-4fad-9749-cf352ad0ba1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824085845","data":{"timestamp":" 946824085845"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" d9d6a230-521d-4fad-9749-cf352ad0ba1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_L-N-J"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824089751","data":{"timestamp":" 946824089751"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" d9d6a230-521d-4fad-9749-cf352ad0ba1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_F-M-N"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824093249","data":{"timestamp":" 946824093249"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" d9d6a230-521d-4fad-9749-cf352ad0ba1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_P-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824096757","data":{"timestamp":" 946824096757"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" d9d6a230-521d-4fad-9749-cf352ad0ba1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-T-N"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824102276","data":{"timestamp":" 946824102276"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" d9d6a230-521d-4fad-9749-cf352ad0ba1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-I-G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824108033","data":{"timestamp":" 946824108032"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" d9d6a230-521d-4fad-9749-cf352ad0ba1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-I-G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824118267","data":{"timestamp":" 946824118267"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 504eae6a-591f-40e1-85f9-d0f664bac068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824123291","data":{"timestamp":" 946824123291"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 504eae6a-591f-40e1-85f9-d0f664bac068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-4-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824128764","data":{"timestamp":" 946824128764"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 504eae6a-591f-40e1-85f9-d0f664bac068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_1-3-0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824133676","data":{"timestamp":" 946824133676"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 504eae6a-591f-40e1-85f9-d0f664bac068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-4-8"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824138468","data":{"timestamp":" 946824138468"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 504eae6a-591f-40e1-85f9-d0f664bac068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-4-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824143748","data":{"timestamp":" 946824143748"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 504eae6a-591f-40e1-85f9-d0f664bac068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-1-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824148633","data":{"timestamp":" 946824148633"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 504eae6a-591f-40e1-85f9-d0f664bac068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-6-8"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824153784","data":{"timestamp":" 946824153784"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 504eae6a-591f-40e1-85f9-d0f664bac068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_4-5-8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824159053","data":{"timestamp":" 946824159053"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 504eae6a-591f-40e1-85f9-d0f664bac068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_0-5-3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824165415","data":{"timestamp":" 946824165415"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 504eae6a-591f-40e1-85f9-d0f664bac068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824171353","data":{"timestamp":" 946824171353"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 504eae6a-591f-40e1-85f9-d0f664bac068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824191865","data":{"timestamp":" 946824191865"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 5ed4bdbc-d089-45bd-84b8-37be269da86b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_N_H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824198541","data":{"timestamp":" 946824198541"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 5ed4bdbc-d089-45bd-84b8-37be269da86b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_N_F"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824205153","data":{"timestamp":" 946824205153"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 5ed4bdbc-d089-45bd-84b8-37be269da86b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_O_E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824211826","data":{"timestamp":" 946824211826"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 5ed4bdbc-d089-45bd-84b8-37be269da86b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_P_Y"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824218487","data":{"timestamp":" 946824218487"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 5ed4bdbc-d089-45bd-84b8-37be269da86b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_F_R"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824225112","data":{"timestamp":" 946824225112"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 5ed4bdbc-d089-45bd-84b8-37be269da86b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_K_W_N"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824231723","data":{"timestamp":" 946824231723"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 5ed4bdbc-d089-45bd-84b8-37be269da86b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_N_P"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824238326","data":{"timestamp":" 946824238326"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 5ed4bdbc-d089-45bd-84b8-37be269da86b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_N_Y"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824244972","data":{"timestamp":" 946824244972"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 5ed4bdbc-d089-45bd-84b8-37be269da86b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_N_D"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824251659","data":{"timestamp":" 946824251658"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 5ed4bdbc-d089-45bd-84b8-37be269da86b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_N_G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824264786","data":{"timestamp":" 946824264786"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 5ed4bdbc-d089-45bd-84b8-37be269da86b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_Y_N_G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824417271","data":{"timestamp":" 946824417269"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 5ed4bdbc-d089-45bd-84b8-37be269da86b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_Y_N_G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824417378","data":{"timestamp":" 946824417378"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" a94c74b6-7547-4a82-a0b2-47cf41cb82d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajua kuwa alilipa nauli yake kamili!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMILI"," userResponse":" KAMILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824428574","data":{"timestamp":" 946824428574"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 79e75cd4-8c3b-4f51-ac37-6b02f8c898ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824431729","data":{"timestamp":" 946824431729"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 79e75cd4-8c3b-4f51-ac37-6b02f8c898ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824435735","data":{"timestamp":" 946824435735"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 79e75cd4-8c3b-4f51-ac37-6b02f8c898ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824439913","data":{"timestamp":" 946824439913"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 79e75cd4-8c3b-4f51-ac37-6b02f8c898ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824444073","data":{"timestamp":" 946824444073"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 79e75cd4-8c3b-4f51-ac37-6b02f8c898ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824447910","data":{"timestamp":" 946824447910"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 79e75cd4-8c3b-4f51-ac37-6b02f8c898ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824452522","data":{"timestamp":" 946824452522"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 79e75cd4-8c3b-4f51-ac37-6b02f8c898ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824456811","data":{"timestamp":" 946824456811"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 79e75cd4-8c3b-4f51-ac37-6b02f8c898ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824463513","data":{"timestamp":" 946824463512"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 79e75cd4-8c3b-4f51-ac37-6b02f8c898ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824465480","data":{"timestamp":" 946824465480"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 79e75cd4-8c3b-4f51-ac37-6b02f8c898ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824484921","data":{"timestamp":" 946824484921"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824486215","data":{"timestamp":" 946824486215"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824502406","data":{"timestamp":" 946824502406"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824514893","data":{"timestamp":" 946824514893"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824527770","data":{"timestamp":" 946824527770"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824539101","data":{"timestamp":" 946824539101"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824550780","data":{"timestamp":" 946824550780"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824562202","data":{"timestamp":" 946824562202"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824572970","data":{"timestamp":" 946824572970"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824579331","data":{"timestamp":" 946824579331"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824591475","data":{"timestamp":" 946824591475"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824606353","data":{"timestamp":" 946824606353"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824620144","data":{"timestamp":" 946824620144"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824627496","data":{"timestamp":" 946824627496"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824627766","data":{"timestamp":" 946824627766"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824640805","data":{"timestamp":" 946824640805"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824650576","data":{"timestamp":" 946824650576"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824656282","data":{"timestamp":" 946824656282"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824666190","data":{"timestamp":" 946824666190"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824675745","data":{"timestamp":" 946824675745"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824686086","data":{"timestamp":" 946824686085"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824697545","data":{"timestamp":" 946824697545"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824708279","data":{"timestamp":" 946824708279"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824716412","data":{"timestamp":" 946824716412"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 3c5ac1d4-8123-41f5-b655-a8a1d4eca079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824754823","data":{"timestamp":" 946824754823"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" e21a6ec1-b1ba-457c-9f71-eb973d2900a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824757665","data":{"timestamp":" 946824757665"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" e21a6ec1-b1ba-457c-9f71-eb973d2900a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824762499","data":{"timestamp":" 946824762499"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" e21a6ec1-b1ba-457c-9f71-eb973d2900a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824762567","data":{"timestamp":" 946824762567"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" e21a6ec1-b1ba-457c-9f71-eb973d2900a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUTANO"," userResponse":" MAKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824781011","data":{"timestamp":" 946824781011"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 63b1d595-afdd-4568-8705-809263f9d6a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824786144","data":{"timestamp":" 946824786144"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 63b1d595-afdd-4568-8705-809263f9d6a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824791200","data":{"timestamp":" 946824791200"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 63b1d595-afdd-4568-8705-809263f9d6a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824796196","data":{"timestamp":" 946824796196"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 63b1d595-afdd-4568-8705-809263f9d6a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824801260","data":{"timestamp":" 946824801260"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 63b1d595-afdd-4568-8705-809263f9d6a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824806844","data":{"timestamp":" 946824806844"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 63b1d595-afdd-4568-8705-809263f9d6a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824815174","data":{"timestamp":" 946824815174"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 63b1d595-afdd-4568-8705-809263f9d6a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946824862024","data":{"timestamp":" 946824862024"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_172839"," gameId":" 63b1d595-afdd-4568-8705-809263f9d6a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}